<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Britam</string>

    <string name="britam_biashara_content">This is a simplified combined solution tailored for SMEs. It is designed as a self-rated product, where the customer chooses the different solutions. Political Violence &amp; Terrorism Cover are extended up to a limit. Britam Biashara also offers relaxed Warranties &amp; Conditions. </string>
    <string name="theft_insurance_content">This provides cover for theft or attempted theft of goods occurring at the Insured\'s business premises, resulting from forcible or violent entry or exit.</string>
    <string name="cyber_insurance_content">Cyber liability insurance is designed for all businesses, Corporates, Small and Medium Enterprise entities. The cover protects your business against common cyber threats, such as ransomware, and against new techniques used by criminals to steal or interrupt data. The most common threat is data breaches and losses e.g., network security breaches, loss of private data and theft of intellectual property.</string>
    <string name="fire_insurance_content">Fire Insurance provides protection against loss in the event of a fire. This insurance policy covers loss or damage to property caused by fire, lightning, explosion, earthquake, bushfire, riot and related perils.</string>
    <string name="liability_insurance_content">Liability insurance offers protection to purchasers against third party insurance claims.</string>
    <string name="political_insurance_content">Terrorism and political violence (PVT) insurance covers an individual or company against physical loss and damage, as well as business interruption costs, because of a terrorist act or acts of political violence such as riot, strike, civil commotion, revolution, war, civil war, rebellion, insurrection, sabotage, coup d’état and malicious damage, and consequential looting. It can occur as a stand-alone cover or as part of another policy such as Motor Vehicle insurance or Home Insurance commonly called a rider.</string>
    
    <string name="home_insurance_content">Home insurance covers your house and belongings against life\'s unexpected events. It covers you against theft, damage by extreme weather, fire, and other losses. Generally, home insurance is categorized by two types of cover — buildings and contents. These can be combined or bought separately for total peace of mind, so the first step is deciding which option is better for you.</string>
    <string name="motor_insurance_content">At Britam, we understand how much you cherish your car and the need to protect it at all times.
            That\'s why we offer comprehensive motor insurance to keep your prized possession safe and sound.
            Our policy covers accidental damage or overturning, loss or damage by fire and theft, malicious damage, and third party liabilities. </string>
    <string name="burglary_content">Any individual who wants to cover his / her home or business can take this cover. It is a simple and affordable cover option, and its fixed benefit options with premiums quoted upfront provides flexibility to choose as per your needs or requirements. The Optional Business Interruption benefit also gives freedom to choose as per requirements and needs.</string>
    <string name="accident_content">There are two categories</string>
    <string name="family_plans_content">There are four categories</string>
    <string name="funeral_content">There are two categories</string>
    <string name="mmf_content">This is a type of unit trust fund that invests in low-risk investments with an element of stable returns such as fixed deposit accounts, treasury bills or in a commercial bond. A money market fund invests mainly in fixed income securities with short investment duration and high credit quality.</string>
    <string name="bond_plus_content">This is an income fund which invests in a variety of bonds including corporate bonds, treasury bonds and other fixed-income securities, minimizing the risk involved with investing directly in bonds. It allows for immediate liquidity, giving an edge over bonds in the market which are not easily disposed of. The income fund looks to achieve a reasonable level of current income with maximum stability for the capital invested. The Fund is suitable for investors seeking a regular income from their investment periodically, ideally after a 2 – 3 year period.</string>
    <string name="balanced_content">Our balanced fund is a unit trust that invests in diversified asset classes including fixed income assets, offshore, property and equity. It provides investors with medium to long term growth of their capital. It is a medium risk investment vehicle and is suitable for a 3–5 year investment horizon. The diversification boosts return by providing a cushion during a downturn in one asset class.</string>
    <string name="equity_content">This fund aims to offer superior returns over the medium to longer term by maximizing long term capital growth by investing primarily in listed companies on the Securities Exchanges of Kenya, Uganda and Tanzania. The fund has some exposure to offshore listed companies, denominated in Euro, Sterling Pound or US Dollar. It is a suitable investment option for investors looking to put money in the stock market but lack the professional capacity to select and manage their equity portfolio. It is also ideal for investors with a long term investment horizon of 5 years or more.</string>
    <string name="endowmend_content">An endowment fund is the ideal investment tool for organisations that receive donations and grants such as non-profit organizations, museums, churches, or hospitals. It is an investment fund established by the foundation and managed by Britam Asset Managers. The fund makes consistent withdrawals from invested donations which acts as capital.</string>
    <string name="gratuity_content">Britam Asset Managers in collaboration with organisations set up Gratuity Funds which are defined retirement benefit plans offered by companies to employees upon leaving their jobs. Gratuity payment and its applicable terms and conditions are stipulated in one’s employment contract as well as the employer’s policies. These funds offer various benefits being a valuable part of the overall remuneration package.</string>
    <string name="unknown_content">Visit our website</string>
</resources>